Apple Pie
Apple pie?
Not apple.
You think?
100 times more apple pie.
I wanted to give you the experience of eating it.
It's hard to believe it's alcohol.
It's delicious.
I'm completely swamped.
Thank you.
It's delicious.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Ayaka Sasaki from Peach Color Clover Z.
Oh, I'm sorry, I made a mistake introducing myself.
I'm Ayaka Sasaki, the public relations manager of Infinite Company Stapler.
I look forward to working with you.
Well, what a new program of Mugen Company STAPLA has started!
The idols belonging to Infinity Company Stapla will be putting their skills to use
and collaborate with corporate groups all over Japan with no rules
We hope that you will enjoy the show and become energized.
We hope to make this show a fun and energetic one.
This time, we will be collaborating with
Mr. Yoshida, the president of Umenoyado Sake Brewery in Nara, with whom we are going to collaborate
Mr. Yoshida, the president of Umenoyado Sake Brewery in Nara, who we are going to collaborate with, invited us to his head office.
He invited us to his head office to learn more about Umenoyado Sake Brewery.
I was invited to the head office as Ayaka Sasaki, the idol of Umenoyado Sake Brewery.
but also as Ayaka Sasaki, who is in charge of public relations
I'm a little nervous, but
I'd like to go right away.
Thank you for your time. Welcome.
Thank you very much for joining us today.
I'm Ayaka Sasaki, public relations manager of the human company Stapura. My name is Kayo Shimo of Umi no Edo-shuudo.
Pleased to meet you. - Pleased to meet you.
Thank you very much. Nice to meet you.
You're so nice.
May I call you Arin-san?
No, it's “Arin.” I don't need anything else, so “Arin” will be fine.
Really? Yes. Are you sure? Yes, sir.
I'll call you Arin.
Pleased to meet you. Thank you.
Do you drink alcohol?
I love it!
I'm so happy! Yes, I do!
I often have a drink with my friends.
Today, we have a variety of drinks for you to choose from.
We have a lot of different types of drinks, so please come and try them.
Can I? It's such a bright time of day.
We have a lot of different types of drinks.
We're making various types of sake that go beyond the image of alcohol.
We make many different types of sake, so please enjoy them all!
I'm looking forward to it! I'm going to be able to drink a lot!
It's in that new space, so let's go!
Let's go! Thank you very much.
I'll be right there.
Thank you very much for your time. Please come in.
There are so many different kinds of sake. So colorful.
Just a quick look, there are so many kinds here. Thank you very much.
So this is a directly managed store attached to the brewery.
So they make the sake and sell it right here.
We've been in business for 132 years this year.
I thought it was new because it was so beautiful, but you know, generally people say that 132 years is a long history, but the sake industry is 200 or 300 years old.
But in the sake industry, it's usually 200 or 300 years old.
I'm sorry, it's only a little over 100 years old? We are such a sake brewery that people say we are young.
Therefore, we always try to challenge new things with the feeling of a newcomer.
That's what we do best.
That's really cool.
Thank you very much.
This is the sake that we originally made.
We have been making only sake for over 100 years.
Sake is something that is made in winter.
That's right, I drink it without thinking about it.
I'm fine.
Don't be honest at all.
The most important thing is that it tastes good.
It's winter, isn't it?It's winter, isn't it?
Yes, sake is made in winter.
It's fine to make sake in winter.
But in the summer, you have too much to do.
That's right, I don't know what I should do.
Yes, I have free time in the summer.
So, what can I do in the summer?
The ume (plum) season is May, June and July.
So I decided to make plum wine that can be harvested at that time of the year.
Usually plum wine is soaked in shochu or white liquor, but we decided to soak them in our own sake, so we developed a sake-based plum wine.
That's why we developed a sake-based plum wine.
Our sake is not dry, but rather umami, sweet and very soft.
It has a sweetness and a softness, and the higher the quality of the sake, the more it melts in your mouth.
It looks easy to drink.
Umeshu made with this sake is sweeter and easier to drink.
Sweet and easy to drink
That's right.
And this plum wine is right here.
I was wondering how colorful it is.
First of all, this black bottle of plum wine.
When we launched this plum wine, it was a big hit because it's sake-based, so it's very soft and tasty.
But then we had another problem... we were left with a lot of plum seeds after soaking them in plum wine.
What to do with them? We had to pay for them and throw them away as industrial waste.
So we thought we'd do something about it, and came up with this.
This product is called Aragoshi Umeshu, and it's absolutely delicious!
You can see that after the plums are soaked in plum wine, the seeds are removed and ground up.
You can see the plum pulp is grinded and mixed into the drink.
It's a plum wine with texture, isn't it?
It's a plum wine with the texture of eating.
It was a big hit.
And from this point on, we also started to make this kind of plum wine.
We were thrilled that this kind of drink could be enjoyed so much.
We also felt a sense of excitement.
And that's how we came to realize that
Yuzu sake, peach sake
Peach wine
Pineapple
We will serve various kinds of sake. I'm going to put out a lot of different things.
Like this mix.
It's rare.
Almost no mixing.
There's a lot of pulp in it already.
It's very pulpy like this.
It's really exciting.
It's a really exciting sake with a lot of pulpiness.
So this fruit wine is also sake-based?
Yes, it is.
I'm not so good at it these days.
Even if you're not so good at it, you can suddenly feel familiar with it and want to try it if it's roughly dried or fruity. It's just the way it is.
We often use the word “excitement”.
We value the word “excitement” very much, and in order to be excited, we need to be surprised and impressed to create excitement.
And in order to create excitement, we have to challenge ourselves to try new things.
We are very proud of the fact that we are able to create a wide variety of products that are so good.
This is a sake bottle, and it's not in a bottle but in a portion, so it's easy to take with you and drink anywhere.
You can drink it anywhere.
You can carry it in a small bag.
Wow!
How cute!
That's right, we place great importance on the excitement of being able to do something like this with alcohol, and that's why we create products like this.
That's why there are so many products like this.
Thank you very much.
Now then, what is the best way to get people to know about our company?
I think the best way to get to know our company is to drink our products.
I'm very happy.
It's really great to be here in such a beautiful space.
Are you sure you don't mind if I have a drink?
Of course, we hope you'll be excited.
I'm already a little excited before I drink it.
I'd like to take you up on your offer.
First of all, let's start with this Aragoshimikana.
It's a product with lots of pulpy mash.
It smells just like an orange, just like a mandarin orange!
Bon appétit!
It's full of pulp!Lots of pulp coming in!
Do zo do zo do zo do zo.
The mikan pulp comes in and it's sweet and delicious!
It's as if you're drinking a rich mikan, squeezed to perfection!
Yes, you really don't feel the alcohol in this.
I thought it would be like juice.
It's more like juice, really.
I can guzzle it!
This is only the first glass.
Hey!
Don't you want more?
No, it's a little bit, you know.
I've already had a taste of it. I think it's pretty good.
I think it's delicious.
So, we have doubled the mashed mandarin oranges
and doubled the size of the mandarin oranges I mentioned earlier.
10 mandarin oranges?
That's right. It's the equivalent of 10 whole mandarin oranges!
Bob-bob-bob-bob-bob-bob!
Dobobobobobobo!
Oh, it's so full! Wow!
It's just that...
It's so heavy!
Bon appétit!
Oh, my God!
So much mandarin orange!
The weight is heavier than the water.
There's so much firepower, I feel like I'm going to be full.
When I was at the restaurant, I was wondering if it's easy to drink if you don't like alcohol.
I thought it would be easier for those who don't like alcohol to drink it by mixing it with something else.
It would be a waste to drink it without it!
I hope you'll drink it with this cold meaty feeling.
Next, we have a sweet sake.
It's a drink?
It's a sweet to drink.
It's part of a new series.
It's called “Adult Nighttime Sweets”. It's a series called Adult Night Out Separate.
That's great.
We want you to enjoy it on an adult night with a separate stomach, right?
Apple pie.
Apple pie?
Not apple.
Apple pie.
How's that again?
That's great.
I'll have some more.
Yes, sir.
Apple pie.
All I can say is, it's apple pie.
That's what I think.
A hundred times apple pie.
It's not crispy apples.
It tastes like moist apples that have been soaked.
It's got that savory pie taste.
I think it tastes a little bit like a pie, and a little bit like a pie, and a little bit like a pie, and a little bit of that sloppy
The moist apple taste and the pie taste in your mouth.
and the pie in your mouth.
Oh, yeah, it's perfect.
Yeah, that's why...
I mean, it's just... it's just...
Recreate it.
Yes, that's right.
It's made with oats milk to give it a doughy texture.
Right, so it's definitely not a crunchy pie.
It's a pie when it comes in your mouth.
Oh, that's interesting!
It's a little bit different, but it's like curry is a drink.
You know, metaphorically speaking.
That's reality!
It really is!
I'm so happy, I'm so happy!
It's a different flavor. It's a different flavor.
This is...
Please take the quiz and guess what flavor it is.
I'd like you to guess what flavor it is.
Well then, let's use our experience from earlier.
It's not apple flavor, but something like apple pie.
The name of the dish?
Yes, I guess so.
It looks a little like grapes or something.
It has a berry-like appearance.
Strawberry? It's a little sweeter than I expected, or sweeter than crispy.
It tastes like bean jam.
Yes! And the bean jam!
It tastes like red bean paste,
But there's... The red bean paste skin!
And that chewy texture!
Oh!
You have it?
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
Oh, my God, strawberry Daifuku!
You're right! You're right!
Strawberry Daifuku! Definitely!
The texture is really the grains of this bean paste,
And there are strawberry-like ones, too!
Is there mochi (sticky rice cake) in there too?
Is there sticky rice cake in it?
There is no mochi in it.
But we have a special technique to make you feel it.
Wow! It's like there's mochi chopped up.
It tastes like mochi chopped into pieces.
Thank you very much.
I'm so glad you can feel it.
It's amazing.
It was a super Daifuku, totally.
Next time.
I'd like you to have the experience of pouring and eating sake.
No, alcohol is not for drinking. No, you don't drink alcohol.
By all means, eat.
But there's a little ice cream in front of you.
That's right.
It's called “Adult Fruit Swamp.” It's a little bit strawberry.
You can drink it and eat it, too.
But as you can see, the pulp is huge!
Wow!
What do you think? How is it?
A little more...
Ah! How is it? Is it good?
It's good! It's good!
Yes! Okay, then! Thank you!
But I...
If you hadn't told me, I wouldn't have guessed it was alcohol...
I don't think so.
Bon appétit!
Yes!
It's delicious! That's great! It's delicious!
I feel like I'm eating strawberries!
Strawberries!
I don't feel like I'm drinking alcohol.
Yes!
I think so!
I'm completely swamped!
Thank you!
It's delicious!
Did you get swamped?
I'm swamped! Oh my God!
This is fun! And really!
I'm so happy!
I can make my own arrangements.
I'm excited to think of my own arrangements
I'm excited to think about it
I think it's fun to do it!
I'm so happy! Thank you very much!
There is also a mango in this series.There is also a mango in this series.
Mango can be mixed with yogurt to make a mango lassi.
Mango Lassi can be made by mixing it with yogurt.
Perfect with curry!
The newest item in this series is
The newest item in this series is a peach from the swamp
Peaches from this swamp.
Peaches have a very high water content to begin with.
Peaches that you can eat even with a full stomach.
And now
And now in this shape
You can eat as many as you want.
I'd like you to take a sip and think about what would go well with this.
I'd like you to think about what would go well with this.
Delicious!
Peach.
It's so refreshing and easy to drink.
Yes, it certainly is.
Like a fruit punch.
Nata de coco...
I think it looks delicious even if it's jelly-like
I think it's delicious even if it's jelly-like.
I like tea.
I like tea. I like tea.
I think it would be delicious
I think it looks delicious.
Wrap some ham around cheese and put some of this on it.
and put a little bit of this on it.
Stylish!
Looks so delicious!
It's so stylish!
I'm a little surprised at myself.
I thought I wanted to eat something a little salty.
Meat?
What? But it's not like fried food, is it?
But I thought it could be used for spring rolls, sweet chili sauce, or something like that.
Thank you very much for the great idea.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you for what we were able to support so much.
Simply put, it was delicious.
I love to drink so of course I enjoyed it though,
I really felt a bit cheated by those who are not so much romanganized by alcohol,
I was very excited about the taste, which I really hope you will try anytime you drink it.
Thank you very much.
I am most happy that you said you were excited.
Let me shop at the food store a little later.
With pleasure.
We definitely want to make this collaboration a success. Yes, I will.
Yes, I would like to go back to the plan of the endless outings and consult with the outing group to make it even more enjoyable.
Now then, I will do my best to make this collaboration between Ume-no-Yado Sake Brewery's adult flesh swamp peaches and Ayaka Sasaki of Peach Color Clover Z a good one, so please look forward to this Momo-numa collaboration.
Please look forward to this Momonuma collaboration.